{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "How long is the average shower in your household?",
			"type": "HouseHold",
			"answers": [
				{ "Under 5 min": 200 },
				{ "5-15 min": 300 },
				{ "Over 15 min": 400 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you take baths? If so, how often?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "1 bath per day": 100 },
				{ "2 baths per day": 130 },
				{ "No": 0 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you have low-flow shower heads?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [{ "Yes": 210 }, { "No": 250 }, { "Some": 0 }]
		},
		{
			"question": "How long do you leave your bathroom faucets running each day?(Answer for your entire household and include brushing your teeth and shaving.)",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "Under 5 min": 320 },
				{ "5-15 min": 340 },
				{ "Over 25 min": 350 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "How long do you leave the kitchen faucet running each day?(Answer for your entire household and include everything but washing dishes.)",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "Under 5 min": 320 },
				{ "5-15 min": 340 },
				{ "Over 20 min": 390 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Does your kitchen sink have a low-flow faucet?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [{ "Yes": 210 }, { "No": 10 }, { "Maybe": 0 }]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you let it mellow?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [{ "ofCourse": 210 }, { "Sometimes": 100 }, { "No": 10 }]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you have low-flow toilets?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [{ "Yes": 210 }, { "No": 10 }, { "Sometimes": 100 }]
		},
		{
			"question": "How do you wash your dishes? ",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "With hands": 210 },
				{ "Dishwasher": 150 },
				{ "Trash them or eat out": 50 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "How do you do laundry? ",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "With hands": 210 },
				{ "Washing Machine": 190 },
				{ "Laundromat(pay someone else)": 10 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you have a greywater system installed in your home?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "Heck, yes": 210 },
				{ "No": 190 },
				{ "Sometimes": 10 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you water a lawn or garden?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [{ "Yes": 210 }, { "No": 190 }, { "Sometimes": 10 }]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you have a swimming pool?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "Yes": 210 },
				{ "No": 190 },
				{ "Maybe in future": 10 }
			]
		},
		{
			"question": "Do you have a car?",
			"type": "Personal",
			"answers": [
				{ "Yes": 210 },
				{ "No": 190 },
				{ "Maybe in future": 10 }
			]
		}
	]
}
